You think you've
heard every Batman story.          译制者:  哔哩哔哩@poi字幕组
你以为你知晓每一个蝙蝠侠故事
I promise, you haven't.
我向你保证,并不是每一个
I wouldn't have
believed it myself
如果不是亲眼见证的话
if I hadn't seen it
with my own eyes.
我肯定不会相信
And this time, curiosity
almost killed this cat.
而这一次,好奇心差点就害死了这只猫
Shut it down, Grodd.
It's over. You're finished!
快把它关掉,格鲁德
一切都结束了!
No, I'm too close.
不,我还差一点
You will not interfere with my
experiment this time, Batman.
你这次可不能妨碍我的实验,蝙蝠侠
Catwoman, don't!
猫女,不要!
What?
什么?
Where am I?
What happened?
我在哪里?
发生什么了?
Hmm?
嗯?
It's Japanese.
And that's me.
上面写的是日语
而那是我
There he is,
get him!
他就在那
抓住他!
Samurai?
日本武士?
Stop! Listen to me, I don't
want to hurt any of you.
停下来听我说,我并不想伤害你们
Fine, have it
your way.
行吧,按你的方式也行
Explain yourself.
说清楚是怎么回事
We were sent to find the man
dressed as a bat.
我们被派去寻找打扮成蝙蝠的人
Our master has ordered us
to kill him on sight.
我们的主人命令我们见则杀
He cannot be allowed to live.
他不被允许活下来
Who's your master?
你的主人是谁?
None of this makes any sense.
这一切都说不通
Everything's offline.
所有功能都脱机了
But from the look of it,
this is ancient Japan.
但是看起来这里是古代日本
Which doesn't explain
what's going on up there.
但解释不了那上面是什么东西
What?
什么
The Joker?
- So soon?
- 小丑?
- 这么快?
That's right, Bats.
没错,小蝙蝠
It is I.
正是吾
Damn you!
去你妈的!
Hi.
嗨~
And Harley Quinn.
以及哈莉奎恩
Oh, but you
have to admit,
哦但是你得承认
we really had you
going there, didn't we?
我们刚刚真把你骗到了,不是吗?
That's enough. What are you
playing at this time, Joker?
够了.你这次想耍什么花招,小丑?
Haven't you heard?
Everyone's been calling me
你没听说吗?
人人都叫我
Diruku Tin Mao,
The Demon King.
第六天魔王
恶魔之王
The most powerful
man in Japan.
全日本最强大的人
But you can call me...
但你也能叫我...
Lord Joker.
小丑尊主
Oh, I never really
wanted to be a Lord.
我也没想要当个领主
It wasn't what you would
call an aspiration.
这并不是我的愿望
But when life throws
you time travels,
但是当人生让你穿越时间
sometimes you gotta make travelade.
有时候你就得稍微旅行一下
Guess I have that monkey
to thank for this.
看来我得为这感谢那只猴子
If it wasn't for
his stupid machine
要不是有他那弱智机器
this tiny island would have never been on my itinerary.
这座小岛根本不会算在我的旅程中
I have to say I've really
enjoyed the sushi here.
我得说我真的很喜欢这里的寿司
Mwah. It's even better
with some sauce.
mua,配上些酱料尝起来更好吃了
Is it me, or is it
getting hot in here?
是我的错觉还是这里变热了?
Oh, don't run away.
I'm your biggest fan.
哦不要跑开啊
我可是你最大的粉丝(扇子
Oh, now, now, Batman, don't
you want to play anymore?
哦蝙蝠侠,你不想再继续玩了吗?
Oh, now look what you've done.
哦,看看你做了什么好事
Poison Ivy would be
very disappointed.
毒藤女会很伤心的
Mmm.
嗯~
Don't you know how bad razor-edged
fighting fans are for the environment?
你不知道锋利的扇子对环境影响有多大吗?
You're the one who
keeps throwing them.
你才是那个一直乱扔的人
Because you won't
let them hit you.
因为你不肯让它们打中你
Looks like you're
fresh out of those fans.
看来你的扇子用完了
So what are you
going to do now, Joker?
现在你要怎么办,小丑?
Oh, I've got options, Bats.
哦我的选项还很多的,小蝙蝠
I've still
got Harley,
我还有哈莉呢
and an army of Samurai who have you surrounded.
以及一支武士军队包围着你
Seven to one,
I'll take those odds.
七对一
我愿意尝试下
Should we go
after him, Lord J?
我们应该去追他吗,J尊主?
I've got people.
我有的是人
Let's just enjoy
the moonlight.
就让我们就享受一下月光吧
We have all the time
in the world.
我们在这个世界有大把时间呢
Move, move.
He can't be far.
动起来动起来
他肯定离这不远
Huh?
哈?
Don't be afraid.
不要害怕
It's just a little catcall.
只是嘘(猫)声而已
Catwoman?
猫女?
When I saw the
Joker's samurai on the move,
当我看到小丑的武士们四处奔波时
I figured
something was up.
我就料到肯定出大新闻了
I'm glad
it was you.
很高兴那是你
How did you
get here?
你怎么到这里来的?
Same as you.
Gorilla Grodd's time machine.
和你一样
大猩猩格鲁德的时间机器
That was
two years ago.
那是两年前的事了
How is that
even possible?
那怎么可能?
I downloaded these before the time jump.
Maybe they can help.
我在时间跳跃前下载了这些
可能会有点用
Say what's
your business, monkey.
说吧你想做什么,猴子
Why have you
brought us here?
你为什么把我们带来这
Criminals of Gotham
City, I've gathered you here
哥谭市的罪犯们
我把你们聚集来这里是为了
To unveil my greatest invention.
公之于众我最伟大的发明
Red Hood,
this is Nightwing.
红头罩
这是夜翼
The lead paid off. It's like
a criminal convention here.
这条线索见成效了
这就像是个罪犯大会
Yeah, I can see them
from here too.
对啊,我从这里也能看到
Well, the Mayor's
party's tonight.
今晚是市长的聚会
I wasn't alone.
我不是单独一人
They were all there too.
他们也都在那
Nightwing, Red Hood,
夜翼,红头罩,
Red Robin, and Robin.
红罗宾,还有罗宾
So where are they?
那么他们在哪里呢?
I don't know.
我不知道
I haven't seen
any of them.
他们一个人我都没见到
But since arriving, Gotham's criminals
have run wild all over Japan.
但自从到了这里,日本到处都是哥谭市的罪犯
Behold, The Quake Engine.
看吧,天体震动引擎
Now, witness as I become
master of time and space,
现在,见证我成为时间与空间的主人
and bend them to my will.
并让时间与空间顺从于我
There are
no more images.
没有更多图像了
The rest are
just audio files.
剩下的只有音频
Grodd's machine must
have affected the data transfer.
格鲁德的机器肯定影响到了数据传输
Now it's all
upside down.
现在状况都反过来了
I think that monkey has been
mucking with our heads.
我认为那只猴子在玩弄我们的脑袋
You will not interfere
with my experiment this time, Bat...
你这次可不能妨碍我的实验,蝙..
So the Joker is just the unwitting
beneficiary of Grodd's experiment.
所以小丑只是格鲁德的实验中
无意中的受益人
Well, no one ever said
he didn't thrive in chaos.
也没有人说过他不会在混乱中更强
But we were there
at the same time,
但是我们当时都在那
why the two year difference?
为什么会有两年的差距?
Who knows how
time travel works?
谁知道时间旅行怎么运作的
Grodd delayed me, and it
must have affected the jump.
格鲁德耽搁了我
而那肯定影响了时间跳跃
A matter of seconds then,
turned to be two years now.
当时只有几秒差距,结果现在却是两年
Selena, may I ask what were
you doing there that night?
赛琳娜,我能问下你那天晚上在那做什么吗?
I can tell you I never thought
I'd end up here.
我只能说我没想到最终会到这个地方来
I followed Gorilla Grodd to Arkham
to see what he was up to that night.
我跟着大猩猩格鲁德到阿卡姆想看看他那晚上想做什么
If it was any good, I was
planning on stealing it.
如果是好东西的话,我本计划着把它偷走的
And the criminals?
而罪犯们呢?
Like the Joker,
they've taken over.
和小丑一样
他们掌权了
They've deceived
all the Sengoku Daimyos
他们欺骗了所有的战国大名
and become
lords of their states.
并成为了几个国的领主
Sengoku Daimyo?
战国大名?
That's right.
没错
This period in Japan was a
feudal era of warring states.
在日本这个封建时代正处于战乱
Yes. Each of Gotham's criminals
is trying to conquer and unify Japan.
没错.每一个哥谭罪犯都想征服并统一日本
The Penguin has seized control
of the state of Kai.
企鹅人掌握了甲斐国
He skirmishes repeatedly with the
neighboring state of Echigo,
他经常与邻国的越后国进行小规模战斗
where Poison Ivy rules.
同样也是毒藤女统治之地
Fly,
my fine-feathered friends.
飞吧,我长翅膀的朋友们
I'll bury you in
the dirt, you old buzzard.
我要把你埋在土里面
你个老秃鹫
In the state of Nutsu,
Deathstroke reigns supreme.
而陆奥国
由丧钟称雄
Once my fortress is complete,
一旦我的要塞完成
it'll be my turn
to strike. Yeah.
就到了我进攻的回合了
Two-Face has taken
control in the state of Omie.
双面人掌握了近江国
Near the capital.
在首都附近
He has become
a vassal of the Joker.
他成为了小丑的诸侯
Let's see, what will
my next move be?
看看我的下一步会是什么
But right now, the feudal
lord who is closest to unifying Japan
但是现在,最接近统一日本的封建领主的人是...
is the Joker.
小丑
So they're all trying to takeover
this country and rewrite history.
他们都想接管这个国家并改写历史
We have to find Gorilla Grodd.
Have you seen him?
我们必须得找到大猩猩格鲁德
你看到过他吗?
Not recently.
最近没有
Why don't you and I
join forces, Bruce?
你我二人何不共同合作呢,布鲁斯?
Join forces?
共同合作?
I want to go home. Two years
is a long time to be away.
我想回家.
两年是很长一段时间了
Okay. But
no tricks, Selena.
好吧
但是不准耍花招,赛琳娜
Swear.
我发誓
We just have to
get into that tower.
我们只需要到那栋塔楼里
Joker keeps Grodd's
time machine in there.
小丑把格鲁德的时间机器放在那
This missionary look
is not bad.
这传教工作做的还不错
There were quite a lot of Christian missionaries
that came to Japan during this era.
在这个时期有很多基督教传教士来到日本
This way you won't look
too suspicious as a westerner.
这样你作为一个西方人看起来也不会很可疑
The bat tonsure
is a nice touch.
这个蝙蝠代头真有品味
Thanks.
谢了
那么,你为什么把我带到这来?
I wanted
you to see this.
我想让你看看这个
The Joker is up to
something strange.
小丑想搞什么奇怪的事情
Is that coal?
那是煤吗?
So the Joker is
already changing the timeline.
看来小丑已经在改变时间线了
The industrial revolution
wasn't until much later.
工业革命还要到很久以后才会发生
I really doubt the Joker
cares much about history.
我很怀疑小丑会不会关心历史
My guess is whatever
he's doing,
我的猜测是不管他在做什么
he'll use it
to become Shogun.
他会用它来成为幕府将军
But it's not
just the Joker.
但是不仅仅是小丑
We'll have to defeat all of
Gotham's criminals to save history.
我们得打败所有哥谭罪犯来拯救历史
We'll need weapons
for that.
我们需要武器
If only there were
someone who could help us.
要是要哪个好哥哥能来帮我们就好了
Care for
some tea, sir?
要喝茶吗,少爷?
Ah, much appreciated.
啊,非常感谢
Oh, is this is black tea?
哦,这是红茶吗?
Hard to come by in these
neck of the woods.
在附近一带很难见到这种东西
Hope you find it
to your liking.
希望你会喜欢
Alfred.
阿尔弗雷德
It was Ms. Selena's idea.
I do apologize.
是赛琳娜女士的主要
我很抱歉
It's a bit more rustic
than you're accustomed to.
它比你习惯的更加粗糙
But I think it makes for
a suitable bat cave.
但是我认为用来做蝙蝠洞很合适
What?
什么?
I can't believe
you didn't tell me, Selena.
不敢相信你没有告诉我,赛琳娜
I know, but I wanted to see the
look of surprise on your face.
我知道,但是我想看到你吃惊的表情
There's no need
to worry.
不用担心
The vehicle's been well
maintained, Master Bruce.
载具被保养的很好,布鲁斯少爷
But I don't understand.
但是我不明白
Alfred was in
the Batmobile that night.
那天晚上阿尔弗雷德在蝙蝠车里
We were lucky enough
to find each other here.
我们能在这里找到对方很幸运
And we both figured it was only a
matter of time before you arrived.
而我们俩都认为你到这里是早晚的事
And here I am.
而现在我到了
Well, I think the Joker would be
quite shocked to see you in it.
我认为小丑看到你在这车里面一定会很震惊
Yeah, let's hope.
对啊,让我们希望吧
Well, I must confess
好吧,我得坦白
that I'm quite relieved Ms. Selena
found you in the forest, Master Bruce.
赛琳娜女士能在森林里找到你我很开心,布鲁斯少爷
I, for one, have always wanted
to visit this beautiful country,
我一直都想拜访这个美丽的国家
but I'd much prefer to
do so in my own time.
但是我选择在我的时间线这么做
Although, I must admit, I've picked
up quite a few new culinary ideas.
不过我得承认我在这里学到了几个烹饪主意
And there's a fish I rather
fancy, made with miso.
还有一条鱼我想混着味噌一起吃
I see you haven't changed
at all, old friend.
看来你完全没有变,老朋友
I can't wait to taste this fish
dish you've been talking about.
我等不及想尝尝你一直在说的那条鱼了
Didn't mean to brag, sir,
but it is quite good.
不是我自夸,少爷,但是它尝起来相当好
I'm sure it is.
我相信它肯定是
Get down!
趴下!
Fire!
开火!
A direct hit!
We got him.
直接命中!
我们做到了
- Huh? What is that?
- Bail out.
- 哈?那是什么?
- 撤退
I'm going
after the Joker.
我要去追捕小丑了
Selena, take care
of Alfred for me.
赛琳娜,帮我照顾好阿尔弗雷德
You got it.
收到
Batman's comin'!
蝙蝠侠要来了?
- What's that?
- Batman's here
- 怎么了?
- 蝙蝠侠到了
in his Batmobile!
在他的蝙蝠车里!
Take aim! Fire!
瞄准! 开火!
He's beaten
the gunmen and our cannons.
他击败了我们的枪手和大炮
And he's
rapidly approaching
并且他迅速地到达了
as this fun
puppet show demonstrates.
就和这个搞笑的玩偶演示的一样
He's nothing without
his stupid Batmobile.
他没了他那愚蠢的蝙蝠车什么都不是
Which gives me
an interesting idea.
这让我想到了一个有趣的点子
Nice try.
想得美
Oh, Batman. The old
magnetized bumper trick.
哦蝙蝠侠.祖传的磁性保险杠技巧
Always so clever
with your technology.
在科技方面总是那么聪明
Harley, activate
Arkham Castle!
哈莉,启动阿卡姆要塞!
But, puddin', the castle
isn't even finished yet.
但是布丁,要塞还没有完工呢
But this is
the Batman!
但是蝙蝠侠来了!
He's the reason we made
it in the first place.
他就是我们最初把它做出来的原因
Right.
对
Get ready, Joker.
准备好了,小丑
What the hell
is that?
那到底是什么?
This is madness.
这太疯狂了
How about a pitcher?
Not a belly itcher.
来一发投手如何?可不是挠肚子的
Now we need a batter,
not a broken ladder.
现在我们需要个击球手,不是坏掉的梯子
Swing batter.
击球!
Incoming.
要来袭了
Now, it's my turn.
到我的回合了
I'm coming for you.
我不会放过你的
Ooh, storming the gate.
哦,从大门冲进来
Let me give you
a helping hand.
让我来帮你一手
Now I'll crush your favorite
toy with you inside it.
现在我要摧毁你最喜欢的玩具,而且你还在那里面
Not today.
改天吧
Very persistent,
my old friend.
真固执啊,我的老朋友
Locked on target.
锁定目标
You know what
I like best about you?
你知道我最喜欢你哪一点吗?
You're so predictable.
你如此的可预测
Bat on a stick, one of
my favorite delicacies.
蝙蝠夹在棍子上,我最喜欢的佳肴
Not so fast.
先别急
It's over, Joker.
You're through.
结束了小丑
你完了
No, I don't think you have
that completely right.
我觉得你没有搞正确
Hmm?
嗯?
How terrible!
真可怕啊!
You can come after me, or save
that mother and child down below.
你可以来追我,或者拯救那个在下面的妈妈和小孩
Your move, Bats!
你的决定,小蝙蝠!
No!
不要!
Bane? How did you...
贝恩? 你是怎么...
This isn't
your fight!
这不是你的战斗!
Go! Hurry!
走!快点!
Need more power.
需要更多力量
Wait! No!
等等!不要!
Get moving,
I'll hold them off.
动起来
我来拖延他们
Hold this!
来拖这个!
Poor Bats. He always
falls for the same tricks.
可怜的小蝙蝠.他总是被同一招骗到
Oh, it makes me sad
he's so dumb.
他这么傻让我好伤心
He's always risking his life
to save ordinary people.
他总是冒着生命危险救普通人
If you had just let them die
and gone after me instead,
如果你直接让他们死反而来追我的话
maybe you wouldn't find yourself
in such terrible shape.
也许你就不会陷入这么糟糕的情况
I have no regrets.
我不后悔
Well, what shall
we do now?
好吧,现在我们该做什么?
Are you just
going to lie there,
你就要躺在那里吗
or are you going to
entertain me some more?
还是说你还要再娱乐我们一下?
I'm not here for
your entertainment.
我可不是来娱乐你们的
Ah, wrong again.
啊,又说错了
Now that all your toys
are busted
现在你所有的玩具都坏掉了
you better start thinking what
you're going to do for a second act.
你最好开始想想下一步应该怎么做
Oh, if only your friends were
around to come by and say hi.
哦,如果你的朋友在附近再来打声招呼的话就好了
Uh, puddin', look!
呃,布丁,快看!
Huh?
蛤?
I didn't mean it!
I was being sarcastic!
我不是认真的!我只是在讽刺!
What? Ninja Batmen?
什么?忍者蝙蝠侠?
We got you.
我们保护着你
Huh?
哈?
Nightwing, Red Robin,
夜翼,红罗宾
who else made the time jump?
还有谁也时间跳跃了?
Red Hood
and Robin, too.
红头罩和罗宾也跳跃了
But Red Hood is away
on a recon mission
但是红头罩去另一个封建国家
to find out what's happening
in the other feudal states.
为了搞清楚状况做侦察任务了
Alfred and Catwoman?
阿尔弗雷德和猫女?
Don't worry.
不用担心
Robin has already
gone after them.
罗宾已经跟着他们去了
They should be
here shortly.
他们应该马上就到了
And him?
而他是谁呢?
Batman, this
is Aeon.
蝙蝠侠,这是永旺
He was a great help to us
after we arrived here.
他在我们刚到的时候帮了我们很多
He's the leader of
the ninja clan.
他是忍者部落的首领
Ninja clan?
忍者部落?
We are the Bat clan
of Hida.
我们是飞驒国的蝙蝠部落
Our lives are guided by
an ancient prophecy.
我们被一条古老的预言所指示
Legend foretells that
when the country is in chaos
传说当国家陷入混乱之中
a foreign ninja wearing
the mask of a bat will come
一名戴着蝙蝠面具之人将到来
and restore order to our land.
并让我们的土地恢复秩序
Bat clan, we have waited
all our lives for this moment.
蝙蝠部落,我们这一生都是为了这一刻
Serve this shinobi
with your life.
用你的生命服侍这位忍者
This is the hour
of our destiny.
这就是我们使命的时刻
Now, we finally look upon you,
现在,我们终于看到你了,
great shinobi from
across the sea of time.
穿越时间之海伟大的忍者
Lord Batman.
蝙蝠侠尊主
Hmm.
嗯
Looks like
a nice place.
看起来是个好地方
Yes, but for
how long.
是,但是能持续多久呢
The Batmobile,
the Batwing, the Batcycle
蝙蝠车
蝙蝠战机,蝙蝠摩托
they've all been destroyed
at the hands of the Joker.
他们都经小丑之手被摧毁了
How do we regain the advantage
when we have nothing?
当我们什么都没有我们要怎样重获优势
Batman.
蝙蝠侠
Monkichi has
a message for you.
Monkichi(小猴子)有消息要给你
Monkichi?
It's weird, but Robin's
made friends with this monkey.
很奇葩,但是罗宾和这个猴子交了朋友
He's really
pretty smart.
他真的挺聪明的
And he understands
everything I say.
而且他听得懂我说的话
What is it?
这是什么?
He says he got it from
someone in the mountain.
他说他是从山里的某位手里得到的
It's in English.
写的是英语
It's Grodd.
是格鲁德
Oh, that feels good.
哦,这感觉真舒服
What is it about
apes and humans
猿和人到底是怎么回事
that we always sigh when we
relax in a hot bath, Batman?
当他们在热水澡里放松时都会叹息,蝙蝠侠?
You might as well
enjoy the waters, too.
你最好也来享受一下
No, I'm good right here.
不必,我在这里挺好的
I never would have taken
you for the shy type,
我没想过你是害羞的那一类型
but then again you are always
hiding behind the mask.
但是你又总是躲在那面具后面
Are you sure you don't
want to reconsider?
你确定你不重新考虑一下吗?
I'm guessing
you didn't invite me here
我猜你邀请我到这里来
just to join you
for a hot soak.
不是单单为了和你一起泡热水澡
Such impatience.
真是不耐心
Well, what did
you expect?
那你以为会怎样?
We're only in this mess
because of you, Grodd.
我们会陷入这堆乱子都是因为你,格鲁德
Why did you invent that time
machine in the first place?
你最初为什么要制造那个时间机器?
That's like asking why this
ancient Gorilla crossed the road.
这就跟问为什么古老的猩猩要过马路一样
Because I could.
因为我能做到
The criminals of Gotham
were my guinea pigs.
哥谭的罪犯只不过是我的小白鼠
I was going to send them some place far
away, so I could take over Gotham myself.
我本来打算把他们传送到很远的地方,这样我就能够独占掌管哥谭了
And I would've succeeded.
而我本来能成功的
The Quake Engine was
my greatest invention.
天体震动引擎是我最伟大的发明
But your interference brought
us to this time and place.
但是你的妨碍让我们来到了这个时间和空间
How's that?
为什么会那样?
We are both responsible
for what transpired that night.
我们都对那天晚上所发生的有责任
And we will need to
cooperate to get home.
而我们需要互相合作以回家
What do
you say, Batman?
你说呢,蝙蝠侠?
I'll be the bait.
我来当诱饵
It's the best way
to draw out the Joker.
这是引出小丑最好的办法
Hmm. Intriguing.
嗯,真有趣
Well, it's been a while,
my dear Gorilla Grodd.
好久不见了,我亲爱的大猩猩格鲁德
Looks like this place
agrees with you.
看来这个地方归你管了
Hmm. Well well, I know
this isn't just a social visit.
嗯...我知道这不单单是一次社交访问
Where's Batman?
蝙蝠侠在哪里?
Clearly you've no time for pleasantries
now that you've set on conquest.
很明显现在你开始征服日本就没有时间享受快乐了
Ooh, is it that obvious?
It's the outfit, isn't it?
哦,有那么明显吗?是服装的效果,不是吗?
Kinda gives it away.
稍微有点暴露了
Imagine this entire country
in total chaos.
想象一下这一整个国家陷入完全混乱
A land full of
needless suffering and pain.
一块充满受难与痛苦的土地
It's very interesting that out of all humans
很有意思在所有人类之中
you're the one who wound up
with the Quake Engine.
你却是那一个拥有天体震动引擎的人
Oh, I'm tired of
all this chit-chat, Grodd.
哦我受够了你的谈天说地了,格鲁德
I told you I'd spare your life
in exchange for the Batman.
我告诉过你我以蝙蝠侠交换会饶你一命
So where is he?
那么他在哪里?
Huh?
哈?
Right here.
就在这里
We have you
surrounded, Joker.
我们把你包围了,小丑
You sure do.
你当然有啊
Catch!
抓住!
No!
不要!
Well, duh!
What do you take us for?
呃
你把我们当什么了?
We knew you'd have men
hiding in the water.
我们知道你有人躲在水下
It's a shame
they all had to die.
真可惜他们都得死
So why don't
you join them?
那么你为什么不一起呢?
Maybe another time.
也许下一次吧
You're still doomed.
你依然在劫难逃
You underestimate
your opponent, Joker.
你低估你的对手了,小丑
Just like you
always do.
就跟往常一样
But how?
We killed you.
怎么做到的?我们明明杀了你
Ever heard of a decoy?
听说过诱饵吗?
Oh.
哦
Sheesh. I never figured you'd
side with Batman, Gorilla Grodd.
天啊.我可真没想到你会和蝙蝠侠合作,大猩猩格鲁德
Anything to gain
the advantage.
能获得优势做什么都行
I never thought
you'd need help
我从没想到你会从一只说话的猴子那里
from a talking monkey
to catch me.
获得帮助来抓我
I'm so embarrassed
for you, Batman.
真为你感到丢人,蝙蝠侠
Don't be. I'm happy
to disappoint.
不必.我很开心让你失望了
Oh, I'd be careful. If he turned
on me, he'll turn on you.
哦要是我的话我就会很小心.如果他背叛了话,他也会背叛你
I'm so grateful we were
able to trust each other.
我很感激我们能相信对方
Many thanks.
非常感谢
But in this world,
trust means nothing.
但是在这个世界,信任什么都不是
Now you will
submit to my control.
现在,你会屈服于我的控制
Bat clan,
destroy them all.
蝙蝠部落,消灭他们全部
We cannot be shaken
by your evil thoughts.
我们不会被你邪恶的思维所动摇
We have mastery over our
bodies and our minds.
我们能控制自己的身体以及思维
So you do.
是吗
Then prepare
to be annihilated.
那么准备好被消灭吧
Over there!
在那边!
Two-face.
双面人
You and Two-Face have
teamed up, Gorilla Grodd?
你和双面人合作了,大猩猩格鲁德?
That's right,
Red Robin.
说的没错,红罗宾
Don't you know Gorilla Grodd
is always two steps ahead?
你不知道大猩猩格鲁德总是领先吗
No!
不!
And to what do I owe this
unexpected visit, Catwoman?
而这次未料到的见面又是为了什么,猫女?
Oh, I thought you might
want this thingy.
哦,我认为你可能想要这个东西
Now where did
you get that?
你从哪里弄到的?
I lifted it from Harley
Quinn during our fight.
我在战斗的时候从哈莉奎恩那里偷来的
It's part of your
fancy quake machine, isn't it?
这是你牛逼哄哄的天体震动机器的一部分,不是吗?
And what do you
want in return?
而作为报答你想要什么?
Take me back
to the future.
带我回到未来
It's a deal.
成交
I thought we could
do business.
我想我们能做生意
We have to
abandon ship.
我们必须得弃船了
Now!
现在!
Joker?
小丑!
Looking for me, Bats?
在找我吗,蝙蝠侠?
Don't do it, Joker.
不要,小丑
We need to go! She can't
stay afloat much longer.
我们得走了!这艘船不能再浮多久了
Take the others, go!
带着其他人,快走!
What about you?
那你呢?
I'm staying. He's
not getting away.
我要留下来,我不会让他逃走的
Oh, I'm really
flattered, Batman.
哦我可真受宠若惊,蝙蝠侠
We really don't spend
enough time together.
我们在一起的时间真的不够
We're just so busy.
我们真的太忙了
To be honest, if Two-Face had killed
you, I'd never forgive myself.
老实说,如果双面人杀了你,我绝不会原谅我自己
I deserve to
kill the Batman.
只有我才配杀死蝙蝠侠
I'm the Joker.
我可是小丑
You're insane.
You'll kill yourself.
你疯了
你会杀死你自己的
Ugh! That's what
I've been trying
呃!我一直都想自杀
to tell you,
you stupid bat.
告诉你吧,你个蠢蝙蝠
I'm having a party,
in hell!
我在地狱里,开派对!
Joker, no!
小丑,不要!
No!
不要!
Hmm. And so it ends.
嗯.于是就这样结束了
Hmm.
Mmm.
The renovations are
almost complete.
革新就快要完成了
Contact the other daimyos.
与其他战国大名联系
The battle will be at
Jigokukohara, the field of hell.
战斗将会在Jigoku kohara进行,地狱原野
We'll see
who'll be shogun.
就来看看谁会成为将军
And when will
we be going home?
那我们什么时候回去?
Now, soon enough.
快了
We still need to obtain three
remaining power converters
我们需要获得剩余的三个能量转换器
from Penguin, Poison Ivy,
and Deathstroke.
从企鹅人,毒藤女,以及丧钟那里获得
Then the Quake Engine will be complete
and we can move through time and space.
然后天体震动引擎就完成了
我们就能在空间和时间内移动
Excuse me, do you mind
stepping aside?
不好意思,你介意让一下吗?
Isn't eating a banana
a little cliche?
吃香蕉是不是有点太陈词滥调了?
Says the cat burglar
in the cat costume.
一个穿着猫戏服的飞贼这么说到
We're relieved you're
with us, Master Bruce.
很宽慰你和我们在一起,布鲁斯少爷
How long have
I been out?
我昏迷多久了?
Two whole days, sir.
整整两天,先生
I see.
这样啊
Well, what is this?
这是什么?
Aeon brought it by, sir.
永旺带过来的,少爷
He said the legendary mask
of the Bat clan
他说蝙蝠部落的传奇面具
should be worn by
its rightful owner.
应该被它正当的主人所穿戴
I had nothing.
我什么也没有了
No vehicles
or weapons.
没有载具
没有武器
I didn't know
who I was anymore.
我当时都不知道自己究竟是谁了
Who was Batman, stripped
of all his technology?
没有了他的科技,蝙蝠侠到底是什么?
In my desperation, I
joined forces with Grodd.
在我的绝望中,我与格鲁德合作了
So many lost and injured
because I was blind
因为我的盲目如此多的死亡与受伤
to Grodd's betrayal,
but ultimately to myself.
由于格鲁德的背叛,
但到最后都是我的错
And yet they still insist
on calling me Master.
然而他们依然坚持叫我领主
So what are
you gonna do?
那么你要怎么办?
Just hang it up?
就这么算了?
What I always do,
I'm going to fight.
就和往常一样,我会战斗
I was wrong.
我错了
I thought
I had nothing.
我以为我什么都没有
But I have more
than I thought.
但是我所拥有的比我想象中的还多
I have my mind,
my body, my spirit...
我有我的意识,我的身体,我的灵魂
and all of you.
以及你们所有人
That's more
than enough.
这比足够更多了
This time and place
has its own rules.
这个时间与地点有它自己的规则
And if we're going to win,
it's time we played by them.
而如果我们要赢,我们就要遵守这些规矩
I swear
我发誓
their faith in me
will not be squandered.
他们对我的信仰不会被浪费
We will master
the ways of the ninja.
我们会精通忍者的行事方式
Our weapons will be
everything that exists.
我们的武器可以是任何东西
And I will turn
their legend
而我会让他们的传奇回归
into reality.
到现实
The techniques of the
ninja are extremely effective.
忍者的技巧及其有效
If we can combine
their martial arts skills
如果我们能将他们的武术技巧
with modern innovations
and combat,
与现代战斗方式结合起来
Grodd won't know what hit him.
格鲁德根本不会知道什么打中他了
If they attack us with their mobile
fortress, we will out-maneuver them
如果他们用他们的移动要塞攻击我们,我们会以计谋胜过他们
and strike back with
everything we've got.
并用尽我们的一切来反击
Will it work?
会有效吗?
The craftsmanship of the
ninja blacksmiths is incredible.
忍者铁匠的工艺简直太不可思议了
The precision of their weapons can't be
matched even by our 21st century standards.
他们武器的精度用21世纪的标准都比不了
The wild game and
produce here are exceptional.
这里的野味与生产特别异常
I'm planning
a high protein diet.
我在计划一项高蛋白质饮食方式
Perhaps some boar steak
for dinner tonight, sir?
今晚也许来点野猪排,少爷?
Sounds good, Alfred.
听起来不错,阿尔弗雷德
When the wheat is ready for harvest,
we can make some freshly baked bread.
当小麦准备好收割了,我们能做一些新鲜的烤面包
Well, you know what they say,
你知道俗话怎么说
wars are won on full stomachs.
肚子不饱怎么打得赢仗
Good thinking.
- Hey!
- 聪明极了.
- 嘿!
Batman, Monkichi
has another message.
蝙蝠侠,Monkichi又带来了一条消息
Has Red Hood
found them?
红头罩找到他们了吗?
Yes.
- I'm on my way.
- 是.
- 我马上就来.
Excuse me.
打扰了
May I have
a cup of water, please?
能请给我一杯水喝吗?
Ah, yes, of course.
好的,当然
Oh,
you must be exhausted.
哦,你肯定累坏了
It's a rather hot day for a
Buddhist monk to be traveling.
对于一个在旅行的佛僧来说这天还真热
I'll break it.
我会把它弄断
Stop! Please stop!
停下来!拜托停下来!
If you don't show
your face, I'll break her arm.
如果你不把你的脸露出来,我会弄断她的胳膊
Okay, okay, okay.
好,好,好
I knew
you were alive, Joker.
我就知道你还活着,小丑
They said you were dead,
but I didn't believe it.
他们说你死了
但是我没有相信
So I've been
looking for you.
所以我一直都在找你
Joker?
小丑?
Why do you keep insisting
on calling me that?
你为什么一直坚持那么叫我?
Admit it!
承认吧!
No! No! My darling!
不!不!我亲爱的!
No, no, are you insane?
不,不,你疯了吗?
You think
I'm that stupid?
你以为我有那么蠢?
Do you expect me
to believe
你想让我相信
the Joker has
taken up farming?
小丑开始做农业了?
Honey?
亲爱的?
You too!
Harley Quinn!
你也是!
哈莉奎恩
Oh, my love.
哦我亲爱的
I owe you this.
我还欠你这个
Please forgive us.
Please. Please.
请原谅我们
求你了,求你了
I don't understand.
我不明白
I'm not
who you think I am.
我不是你认为的那个人
If you're still
going to deny it...
如果你还要继续否认的话
Red hood,stop it!
红头罩,停下来!
Batman, what
are you doing here?
蝙蝠侠,你在这里做什么?
Same as you.
我也想问你这个问题
I heard that you had found
the Joker and Harley.
我听说你找到了小丑和哈莉
Reports of foreign farmers in the
area match their description.
报告说在这个区域的外地农民符合他们的描述
So, you don't
remember anything?
你什么也不记得了吗?
No.
不
We can't remember
anything about our past.
我们想不起我们过去任何一件事了
We came here to live a peaceful
life, deep in the mountains.
我们来这度过一个和平的生活,在深山里
My wife and I, we plough
the fields together.
我的妻子与我,我们一起耕地
I see.
这样
Don't let
'em fool you, Batman.
不要让他们骗了你,蝙蝠侠
They're up to their
same old tricks.
他们又想耍老花招了
I'm not so sure,
Red Hood.
我不确定
红头罩
I'm sorry
for my friend's behavior.
我对我朋友的行为道歉
When I work the land,
I feel like I'm being cleansed.
当我在耕地的时候,我感觉就像我在被净化
It's as if everything bad
inside me is being sucked out
仿佛我身体里的一切坏东西都在被吸出来
and absorbed back
into the earth.
然后被吸收到土地里
I know it sounds silly, but my
wife and I are always saying
我知道这听起来很蠢,但是我的妻子与我一直都在说
it's like
we've been reborn.
就像我们重生了一样
Honey, quick!
Come, look!
甜心,快!
过来, 快看!
There's a sprout.
You have to see this.
发芽了!
你得过来看看这个
New life...
新的生命
A sprout,
are you kidding?
一株幼苗
你在开玩笑吗?
Enough!
够了!
This is different. I've been
tricked by them before.
这不同,我以前也被他们骗过
There isn't the same
madness in his eyes.
在他们的眼里没有同样的疯狂了
If you knew him like I did, you'd know he
could never hide that part of himself.
如果你像我一样那么了解他,你就知道永远都不能隐藏他的那一部分
It's what makes him what he is.
正因为那份疯狂他才是他自己
Oh, honey.
哦,甜心
We did it.
They're finally growing.
我们做到了
他们终于开始成长了
Bruce...
布鲁斯...
He's not the Joker.
At least, not anymore.
他不是小丑
至少,不再是了
They both lost their
memories in the explosion.
他们都在爆炸中失去了记忆
There's no need
to bother them.
不必再烦扰他们了
You can't
be serious.
你不可能是认真的吧
We'll take them
back with us
我们要带他们一起回去
once the Quake Engine
is operational again.
等到天体震动引擎可以再次运行再说
But, for now we'll just
keep an eye on them.
但是现在我们只能多留心了
They're not
going to hurt anyone.
他们不会伤害任何人
Come on,
Red Hood, let's go.
来吧,
红头罩,我们走
I hope
you're right.
我希望你是对的
Construction's complete.
施工完成
The time has arrived to destroy these
upstarts and rebuild the Quake Engine.
已经到了摧毁这些自命不凡的人并重建天体震动引擎的时候了
Arkham Castle, rise!
阿卡姆要塞,启动!
That malicious monkey
is finally on the move.
那条恶毒的猴子终于开始行动了
Let's take what's ours and
feather this nest we've built.
让我们夺回属于我们的东西并让我们的巢穴更加美好
Fly! Trojan Birdman Castle.
飞吧!木马鸟人要塞
Spread your wings!
张开你的双翼!
I will not let
this paradise be destroyed
我不会让这个天堂
被人类的阴谋诡计摧毁
Juroku Plant Poison Castle.
十六毒性植物要塞
Grow. And let them reap
what we have sown.
生长吧.让他们收割我们所播种的
Interesting.
真有趣
Now we'll finally see who's the
most powerful warlord in Japan.
现在我们终于能见证谁是日本最强大的军阀了
Gakuju Sharaso Castle will blow
you all to kingdom come.
Gakuju Sharaso要塞会把你们全都炸到天国去
Fire!
开火!
From order to chaos.
All in the flip of a coin.
从秩序到混乱
全都由抛硬币决定
The enemy converges
at the field of hell.
敌人在地狱原野聚集了
Fudo Omote Two-Face castle will meet
them, and decide the fate of Japan.
Fudo Omote两面人要塞将来会会他们,并决定日本的命运
A fine tea, Alfred.
茶不错,阿尔弗雷德
My pleasure.
我的荣幸
All of the daimyo castles
are on the move.
所有的战国大名要塞都开始行动了
This is our chance.
这是我们的机会
I can't wait to
slaughter them all.
我等不及屠杀他们全部了
Then it will truly earn the
name "The field of hell."
然后"地狱原野"就会真的名副其实了
But what matters is
但是重要的是
the converters and the Quake
Engine will all be in one place.
转换器和天体震动引擎都会在一个地方
This is it.
就是这样了
This is our
one opportunity
这是我们的一个
to defeat them
and return to Gotham.
击败他们并回到哥谭的机会
Remember, the machines,
no matter how large,
记住,这些机器
无论有多么巨大
are still controlled
by humans.
依然是由人类控制
If we can defeat the person
inside the machine,
如果我们能击败机器里的人
then we have
a fighting chance.
那么我们就有机会
Aeon was right.
永旺是对的
I now understand the role
I must play.
我现在明白我的用处了
I am not longer the Batman.
我不再是蝙蝠侠
I will be what the Bat clan
calls me.
我会成为蝙蝠部落所称呼的
I will be their prophecy.
我会成为他们的预言
}I will be the legendary ninja who
will bring peace to their land.
我会成为将和平带给他们土地的传奇忍者
I will be...
我会成为...
Fire!
开火!
This Penguin moves as swiftly
on land as it does at sea!
这只企鹅在陆地上行动和在海上一样快
And it's got
one hell of a bite.
而且它的咬合力可厉害了
Watch it, you bloated bird,
'cause this plant bites back.
看着吧,你这傲慢的鸟,因为这个植物会反击
And I'm going to catch you
in this flytrap.
而我会用这个捕蝇草把你抓住
Trojan Birdman Castle,
木马鸟人要塞
wind forest fire
mountain transformation.
风木火土变形
Two can play
at this game.
我也会这招
Juroku Plant Poison Castle,
十六毒性植物要塞
multitudes of
flowers transformation.
大量花朵变形
Bullseye.
正中靶心
Gakuju Sharaso Castle,
Gakuju Sharaso要塞
rapid fire
hundred cannons transformation.
快速开火上百大炮变形
Fire!
开火!
Not too bad.
不错嘛
Hmph.
哼
Hmm?
嗯?
Gorilla Grodd,
leave him to me.
大猩猩格鲁德,
让我来对付他
Fudo Omote Two-Face Castle,
Fudo Omote双面人要塞
two-faced transformation!
两面变形!
Look! Over there.
快看!在那边
Giant robots?
巨型机器人?
Batman, what now?
蝙蝠侠,现在怎么办?
Master, leave them to us.
领主,把他们交给我们吧
Give 'em hell!
让他们体验一下地狱的滋味!
Behind us.
在我们后面
We're stuck between a rock
and a hard place.
我们现在进退两难了
Come on.
跟上来
Yeah.
I appreciate your
loyalty, Two-Face.
我很感激你的忠诚,两面人
Sure. Until the coin
tells me otherwise.
当然.除非硬币告诉我不要这么做
Tails, I stay.
Heads, I go.
反面留
正面走
Your luck's run out.
你的运气用光了
I'm gonna rip you
limb from limb, Grodd.
我要把你肢解,格鲁德
It's easy to understand
the laws of probability.
概念学很容易理解
It was only
a matter of time.
只不过是时间的问题
Let's go!
我们走!
Head straight for
Arkham Castle!
直接朝阿卡姆要塞走!
Look out!
小心!
Well, that was cool.
那真炫酷
That's
enough games for now.
游戏玩够了
It's time to
get down to business.
是时候开始认真了
What are you doing now?
你现在又在做什么?
All of Gotham's criminals
are now under my mind control.
所有的哥谭罪犯都在我思维控制下了
What they do not know
他们不知道的是
is that I actually manipulated them
into building their fortresses, too.
其实我也操纵了他们建立他们的要塞
Where do you think
they got the technology?
你觉得他们哪来的那种科技?
They are just pieces
in a larger puzzle.
他们只是更大的拼图的一部分
Like the feudal states
of Japan herself.
就连日本这个国家也不过是垫脚石
Whatever it takes
to get home.
能回家付出什么代价都行
Sorry to break it
to you...
很抱歉跟你说
but you're not going anywhere.
但是你哪里也去不了
I'm going to rule
this country
我将会统治这个国家
and turn it into
a kingdom of monkeys,
然后把它变成猿类的国家
and rewrite the history
of the world!
并重写世界的历史!
What is...
这是...
We're back!
我们回来了!
I love giving presents.
我最爱送礼物了
Out with the old
and in with the new.
旧的不去新的不来
No exchanges or returns.
不找零或退款
Joker?
小丑?
It can't be.
不可能
Hi, Bats.
嗨小蝙蝠
You should know by now that you
can't keep a crazy man down.
你现在应该知道了你不能让一个疯人恢复正常
You never want to be
too early to a party.
你肯定不想提前到派对
Right?
不对吗?
Hi, pretty kitty.
嗨,小猫咪
You really took us by surprise
back at the lake, Grodd.
你在湖边真的让我们吃惊了,格鲁德
But now it's time
for a little payback.
但是现在是时候稍微报复一下了
The paralysis isn't permanent, but we're
thinking about increasing the dosage.
麻痹不是永久的,但我们计划增加剂量
Ivy's got the best plants,
don't you think?
艾薇有最好的植物,你不认为吗?
Bastard.
混蛋
Now, now, now,
好了好了好了
don't go
and strain yourself.
不要把自己扭伤了
Not that you
can move anyway.
反正你也不能动
You too, kitty cat.
你也是,小猫咪
Now, in a dramatic turn of events,
the Joker takes over Grodd's plan.
现在,事件戏剧性的变化,小丑接管了格鲁德的计划
Sayonara!
再见了!
Batman!
蝙蝠侠!
It's so tough being a hero.
做一个英雄真难
Are both of you all right?
你们两个都没事吧?
Don't think I didn't notice you
saving Grodd before me.
不要以为我没注意到你先救了格鲁德才救我
But, thank you, Batman.
但是,谢谢你,蝙蝠侠
I see that gas didn't
knock out your attitude.
看来那催眠气体并没有击晕你的态度
I'm glad you're
still with us, Catwoman.
很高兴你还和我们一起,猫女
So what now, puddin'? It looks like this
thing is still plugged into their brains.
现在又怎样,布丁?看来这玩意还插在他们的脑子里
Well, that means it's time
to play a few mind games.
好吧,这就意味着是时候玩几个心理游戏了
Criminals of Gotham,
哥谭的罪犯
become one!
合体!
Five unite and serve
as six heavenly beings.
五个团结,并成为六个神圣的存在
Lord Joker!
小丑尊主!
Whoa! That thing's enormous.
哇!那东西可真巨大
This contraption is better than
I ever imagined, Gorilla Grodd.
这个奇妙的装置比我想象中的还好,大猩猩格鲁德
This country really
will belong the Joker.
这个国家真的会属于小丑了
Now let's see.
现在让我们来看看
What sort of chaos the
super robot can unleash.
超级机器人能释放什么样的混乱
Hurry, get out of here.
快点,离开这儿
Robin, get...
罗宾,离...
Robin!
罗宾!
Gorilla Grodd?
大猩猩格鲁德?
Ooh, that was easy.
Now what?
哦那可真轻松,现在呢?
Guess I could use a nap.
我得睡个小觉
So what now?
现在怎么办?
He's hurt
pretty bad.
他受的伤很严重
Here.
这儿
You can use this.
你能用到这个
It controls my
army of monkeys.
它控制我的猴子军队
Use them to
defeat the Joker.
用他们来击败小丑
I owe you
for saving my life.
你救了我一命,我欠你一次
I promise,
no tricks this time.
我保证,这次不耍花招
Batman, lend us
the flute, please?
蝙蝠侠,把笛子借给我们,可以吗?
Monkichi and I know exactly
what to do.
Monkichi和我知道具体到底该怎么做
What?
什么?
Monkeys?
猴子?
There's millions.
有上百万只
I can feel them. They're
crawling all over me.
我能感觉到他们,他们爬满我身上了
Get off! Get off!
滚下去!滚下去!
They can't hang on.
他们撑不住了
Monmi.
Who's she?
她是谁?
You got it.
了解
So annoying!
好烦人!
If the bad guys are
going to unite, then so will we.
如果坏人要合体那我们也会
Enough monking around!
不许再胡闹了!
I'll blow you to pieces.
我会把你打成碎片
All for one
and one for all.
人人为我
我为人人
Their combined spirit
has formed this giant samurai.
他们集结的精神变成了这个巨大的武士
Now, witness the awesome
power of the monkeys.
现在,见证猴子们伟大的力量吧
Together, they will deliver
a devastating blow!
在一起,他们能使出毁灭性的一击
Unexpected.
这可没料到
Let's move!
开始移动!
Storm the robot
while it's down.
在机器人倒下的时候冲向他
- Right!
- Monkichi,
- 收到!
I'm leaving
the flute with you.
我把笛子留给你
Bruce,I'm going with you
布鲁斯,我和你一起去
Harley Quinn could use
a good ass kicking.
哈莉奎恩需要被痛打一顿
Come on.
跟上来吧
Got to love a man who can forgive
a girl for double-crossing him.
一个能原谅女孩背叛的男人谁不爱呢
Monkey see monkey do.
猴子看到猴子行动
It's not how you fall, but how
you pick yourself up that counts.
重要的不是摔倒而是站起来的过程
All right.
好了
Looks like more
monkey business.
看来又是更多胡闹
Harley, we have guests!
哈莉,我们有客人了!
Why don't you greet them
with a warm kiss?
你何不用温暖的吻欢迎一下他们?
Sure!
当然!
Get down!
趴下!
- Robin.
- No!
- 罗宾.
- 不要!
Master, at your service.
领主,为你效命
What, again? I hate bats!
什么又来?我讨厌蝙蝠!
Go, go, go! Shoo, shoo! Get
out of here, you stupid bats!
滚滚滚!咻咻!滚开你们这群蠢蝙蝠!
Go!
滚开!
Huh?
哈?
Batman?
蝙蝠侠?
Behold, the mighty Batgod
before us.
见证,我们伟大的蝙蝠神
Batman! Harley?
蝙蝠侠!哈莉?
Burn on the field of hell!
让地狱原野烧起来!
We're coming for you.
我们来找你了
Time to settle this...
是时候解决这一切了
once and for all.
一劳永逸地
Party's over, Penguin.
派对结束了,企鹅人
Tell you what, Deathstroke,
跟你说啊,丧钟
I'll give you
the first shot.
我会给你第一枪
I'm gonna wipe
that half-smile...
我会将那个半边脸微笑
right off your face.
从你的脸上抹掉
Poison Ivy, you know
you're not a real plant, right?
毒藤女,你知道你并不是真正的植物,对吗?
I see you're back to
your old self again.
看来你又变回以往的自己了
I was convinced you'd
lost your memory, Joker.
我深信你失去了你的记忆,小丑
Yeah, about that.
对啊,关于那个
I had lost my memory.
I was a decent man.
我的确有失去我的记忆,我成为了一个正派得体的人
What a joke.
真是个笑话
But I had to do it!
但我必须得那么做!
It was the only way
I could get the upper hand.
只有那样我才能获得优势
I hypnotized myself to believe I was
someone else, so you would believe it.
我对我自己催眠让我自己相信我是另外一个人,所以你才会相信
And this little flower was the
trigger to snap me back to insanity.
而这朵小花就是让我恢复疯狂的触发
We did it!
我们做到了!
They're finally growing.
他们终于开始生长了
Harley, get ready.
哈莉,准备好
Can't wait, Mr. J.
等不及了,J先生
See what happens
when you plant a seed
看看你种下一颗种子
and let it grow into
something beautiful?
然后让它长的那么美丽会发生什么?
It's good to return to the
land, get your hands dirty.
能回到农耕很好,把你的手弄脏
The French call it
"Nostalgie de la boue."
法国人把它叫做"Nostalgie de la boue"
Romance of the mud.
污泥的乡愁
You have to admit,
it was a great joke.
你得承认,那玩笑开的很棒
The only way to deceive you
was to deceive myself.
唯一欺骗你的办法就是欺骗我自己
And you fell for it
hook, line and flower.
而你上钩了
Ha!
哈!
The time has finally
come for you to die.
终于到了让你死去的时间了
Puddin', no!
布丁,不要!
Time for some
girl-on-girl action.
时候来来一些女对女行动了
Careful, don't cut yourself.
小心不要伤到自己
It's over, Ivy.
You lost.
结束了,艾薇
你输了
Take your medicine,
kitty-kitty,
好好服药,小猫咪
and say goodnight.
然后说晚安
Keep your tongue
to yourself.
那些话对你自己说吧
Bruce.
布鲁斯
What am I going to do
with you, Batman?
我要跟你做什么呢,蝙蝠侠?
You've destroyed a perfectly
good giant robot castle.
你摧毁了一座完美的巨大机器人要塞
You're going to have to
answer for that.
你得对那做点回应
Let's end this, Joker.
Just you and me.
让我们终结这一切,小丑
只有你和我
With pleasure.
充满荣幸
Oh, I'd hate to come all
the way to ancient Japan
哦我可不想这么一路来到古代日本
and miss out on
a samurai sword fight.
然后错过武士刀对决
Right, Bats?
对吧,小蝙蝠?
Then you
won't be disappointed.
那你不会失望了
Not too bad. Making all
of my dreams come true.
不错嘛,让我的美梦都成真了
- Happy to help.
- Oh, don't tease.
- 很荣幸能帮上忙
- 哦不要开玩笑
You're getting me excited.
你开始让我更兴奋了
That was a good one.
那一招真棒
Oh, you can do
better than that.
哦你肯定比那更好
Maybe you need to hit the dojo
and get some more practice,
也许你应该到道场再多训练一下
work on your feint and parry.
练习一下佯攻和招架
Ooh!
哦!
I'm going to cut you to ribbons, tie
you in a bow, and give you to myself!
我要把你切成缎带,打个蝴蝶结,然后把你送给我自己!
You're going to love it!
你会很喜欢的!
Ooh!
I really doubt that, Joker.
我很怀疑是不是真的,小丑
Sheesh.
哎哟
Must be tough being a hero!
做一个英雄肯定很难吧!
You don't dare kill me!
Isn't that right, Bats?
你不敢杀我!
不对吗,小蝙蝠?
Don't test me!
不要试探我
See, you can't kill me.
看吧,你不能杀我
Oh, the hero
can't finish the job!
哦,这位英雄完成不了工作!
But I can.
但是我能
Just look at how much
fun we're having,
看看我们玩的多开心啊
Batman.
蝙蝠侠
Psych!
吓你的!
You liked that,
didn't you?
你就喜欢那样,不是吗?
It's not over!
还没有结束!
And so it's
finally over, Batman.
终于结束了,蝙蝠侠
You can't trust
everything you see, Joker.
你不能相信肉眼所看到的一切,小丑
Do it. Just let go.
动手,直接放手吧
You can't do it,
can you?
你做不到,你能吗?
The great Batman.
Not such a hero after all!
伟大的蝙蝠侠
终究并不是一个那么好的英雄
Thank you
for all your help.
感谢你所有的帮助
Of course. Our country can now
return to the way it was.
当然,我们的国家现在能回到以前的样子了
We will never forget
what you have done for us.
我们绝不会忘记你为我们所做之事
Thank you, Monkichi.
You were a great help.
谢谢你Monkichi
你真的帮大忙了
It's time for me to go.
I'll never forget you.
我是时候离开了
我绝不会忘记你
Activate
the Quake Engine.
启动天体震动引擎
Master Bruce,
布鲁斯少爷
you'll be needing
this for tonight.
你今晚需要这个
Huh? Ah, right,
of course.
哈?啊,对,当然
Best not to keep
the Mayor waiting.
最好不要让市长久等了
Is the car ready?
车子准备好了吗?
Yes. But it's
rather vintage.
准备好了,但是它相当复古
Tell me, where did you
come across such a rare find.
告诉我,你怎么遇到这么稀有的东西的
I just ran across it
on a trip.
我就是在旅行中碰上的
I always keep my eye out
for interesting souvenirs.
我总是注意着有意思的纪念品
You didn't expect me
to leave empty-handed, did you?
你不会认为我会空手离开吧,有吗?